Guide to the Men's Basketball Game Film Collection, 1947-1996 UA.13.01.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Men's Basketball Game Films
  - Virginia, 1992 January 02
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1992 January 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2867)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1992 January 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2868)
  - Clemson, 1992 January 06
    Duke win; score: 110-67
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1992 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2872)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1992 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2873)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1992 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2874)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1992 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2875)
  - Florida State, 1992 January 06
    Duke win; score: 86-70
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 1, 1992 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2869)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 2, 1992 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2870)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 3, 1992 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2871)
  - Maryland, 1992 January 08
    Duke win; score: 83-66
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1992 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2876)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1992 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2877)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1992 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2878)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1992 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2879)
  - Georgia Tech, 1992 January 11
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1992 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2880)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1992 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2881)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1992 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2882)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 4, 1992 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2883)
  - NC State, 1992 January 15
    Duke win; score: 110-75
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1992 January 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2884)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1992 January 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2885)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1992 January 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2886)
  - UNC-Charlotte, 1992 January 18
    - Duke vs. UNC-Charlotte: Reel 1, 1992 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2887)
    - Duke vs. UNC-Charlotte: Reel 2, 1992 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2888)
    - Duke vs. UNC-Charlotte: Reel 3, 1992 January 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2889)
  - Boston University, 1992 January 21
    Duke win; score: 95-85
    - Duke vs. Boston University: Reel 1, 1992 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2890)
    - Duke vs. Boston University: Reel 2, 1992 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2891)
    - Duke vs. Boston University: Reel 3, 1992 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2892)
    - Duke vs. Boston University: Reel 4, 1992 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2893)
  - Wake Forest, 1992 January 25
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1992 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2894)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1992 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2895)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1992 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2896)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1992 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2897)
  - Clemson, 1992 January 27
    Duke win; score: 112-73
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1992 January 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2898)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1992 January 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2899)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1992 January 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2900)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1992 January 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2901)
  - Florida State, 1992 January 30
    Duke win; score: 75-62
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 1, 1992 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2902)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 2, 1992 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2903)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 3, 1992 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2904)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 4, 1992 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2905)
  - Notre Dame, 1992 February 01
    Duke win; score: 100-71
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 1, 1992 February 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2906)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 2, 1992 February 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2907)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 3, 1992 February 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2908)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 4, 1992 February 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2909)
  - North Carolina, 1992 February 05
    Duke loss; score: 73-75
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1992 February 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2910)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1992 February 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2911)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1992 February 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2912)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1992 February 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2913)
  - Louisiana State, 1992 February 08
    Duke win; score: 77-67
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 1, 1992 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2914)
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 2, 1992 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2915)
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 3, 1992 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2916)
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 4, 1992 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2917)
  - Georgia Tech, 1992 February 12
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1992 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2918)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1992 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2919)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1992 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2920)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 4, 1992 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2921)
  - NC State, 1992 February 16
    Duke win; score: 71-63
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1992 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2922)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1992 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2923)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1992 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2924)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1992 February 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2925)
  - Maryland, 1992 February 20
    Duke win; score: 91-89
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1992 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2926)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1992 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2927)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1992 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2928)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1992 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2929)
  - Wake Forest, 1992 February 23
    Duke loss; score: 68-72
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1992 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2930)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1992 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2931)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1992 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2932)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1992 February 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2933)
  - Virginia, 1992 February 26
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1992 February 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2934)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1992 February 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2935)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1992 February 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2936)
  - UCLA, 1992 March 01
    Duke win; score: 75-65
    - Duke vs. UCLA: Reel 1, 1992 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2937)
    - Duke vs. UCLA: Reel 2, 1992 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2938)
    - Duke vs. UCLA: Reel 3, 1992 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2939)
    - Duke vs. UCLA: Reel 4, 1992 March 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2940)
  - Clemson, 1992 March 04
    Duke win; score: 98-97
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1992 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2941)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1992 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2942)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1992 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2943)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1992 March 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2944)
  - North Carolina, 1992 March 08
    Duke win; score: 89-77
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1992 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2945)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1992 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2946)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1992 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2947)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1992 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2948)
  - Maryland, 1992 March 13
    Duke win; score: 94-87; ACC Tournament, Charlotte, NC
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1992 March 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2949)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1992 March 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2950)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1992 March 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2951)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1992 March 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2952)
  - Georgia Tech, 1992 March 14
    Duke win; score: 89-76; ACC Tournament, Charlotte, NC
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1992 March 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2953)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1992 March 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2954)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1992 March 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2955)
  - North Carolina, 1992 March 15
    Duke win; score: 94-74; ACC Tournament, Charlotte, NC
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1992 March 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2956)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1992 March 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2957)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1992 March 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2958)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1992 March 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2959)
  - Campbell, 1992 March 19
    Duke win; score: 82-56; NCAA Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Campbell: Reel 1, 1992 March 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 127, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2960)
    - Duke vs. Campbell: Reel 2, 1992 March 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 127, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2961)
    - Duke vs. Campbell: Reel 3, 1992 March 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 127, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2962)
    - Duke vs. Campbell: Reel 4, 1992 March 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 127, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2963)
  - Iowa, 1992 March 21
    Duke win; score: 75-62; NCAA Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Iowa: Reel 1, 1992 March 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2964)
    - Duke vs. Iowa: Reel 2, 1992 March 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2965)
    - Duke vs. Iowa: Reel 3, 1992 March 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2966)
    - Duke vs. Iowa: Reel 4, 1992 March 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2967)
  - Seton Hall, 1992 March 26
    Duke win; score: 81-69; NCAA Tournament, Philadelphia, Pa.
    - Duke vs. Seton Hall: Reel 1, 1992 March 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2968)
    - Duke vs. Seton Hall: Reel 2, 1992 March 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2969)
    - Duke vs. Seton Hall: Reel 3, 1992 March 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2970)
    - Duke vs. Seton Hall: Reel 4, 1992 March 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2971)
  - Kentucky, 1992 March 28
    Duke win; score: 104-103; NCAA Tournament, Philadelphia, Pa.
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 1, 1992 March 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2972)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 2, 1992 March 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2973)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 3, 1992 March 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2974)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 4, 1992 March 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2975)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 5, 1992 March 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2976)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Unidentified game film coverage, 1992 March 28; DVD
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Unidentified game film coverage, 1992 March 28; DVD
  - AAU High Fives, 1992 November 18
    - AAU High Fives: Reel 1, 1992 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2977)
    - AAU High Fives: Reel 2, 1992 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2978)
    - AAU High Fives: Reel 3, 1992 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2979)
    - AAU High Fives: Reel 4, 1992 November 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2980)
  - Germany, 1992 November 27
    - Duke vs. Germany: Reel 1, 1992 November 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2981)
    - Duke vs. Germany: Reel 2, 1992 November 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2982)
    - Duke vs. Germany: Reel 3, 1992 November 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2983)
    - Duke vs. Germany: Reel 4, 1992 November 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2984)
  - Canisius, 1992 December 01
    Duke win; score: 110-62
    - Duke vs. Canisius: Reel 1, 1992 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2985)
    - Duke vs. Canisius: Reel 2, 1992 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2986)
    - Duke vs. Canisius: Reel 3, 1992 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2987)
    - Duke vs. Canisius: Reel 4, 1992 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2988)
  - Michigan, 1992 December 05
    Duke win; score: 79-68
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 1, 1992 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2989)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 2, 1992 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2990)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 3, 1992 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2991)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 4, 1992 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2992)
  - Northeastern, 1992 December 07
    Duke win; score: 103-72
    - Duke vs. Northeastern: Reel 1, 1992 December 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2993)
    - Duke vs. Northeastern: Reel 2, 1992 December 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2994)
    - Duke vs. Northeastern: Reel 3, 1992 December 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2995)
  - Rutgers, 1992 December 12
    Duke win; score: 88-79
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: Reel 1, 1992 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2996)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: Reel 2, 1992 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2997)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: Reel 3, 1992 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2998)
    - Duke vs. Rutgers: Reel 4, 1992 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-2999)
  - DePaul, 1992 December 21
    Duke win; score: 89-73; Maui Invitational, Lahaina, Hawaii
    - Duke vs. DePaul: Reel 1, 1992 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3000)
    - Duke vs. DePaul: Reel 2, 1992 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3001)
    - Duke vs. DePaul: Reel 3, 1992 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3002)
  - Louisiana State, 1992 December 22
    Duke win; score: 96-67; Maui Invitational, Lahaina, Hawaii
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 1, 1992 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3003)
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 2, 1992 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3004)
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 3, 1992 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3005)
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 4, 1992 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3006)
  - Brigham Young, 1992 December 23
    Duke win; score: 89-66; Maui Invitational, Lahaina, Hawaii
    - Duke vs. Brigham Young: Reel 1, 1992 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3007)
    - Duke vs. Brigham Young: Reel 2, 1992 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3008)
    - Duke vs. Brigham Young: Reel 3, 1992 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3009)
    - Duke vs. Brigham Young: Reel 4, 1992 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3010)
  - Boston University, 1993 December 30
    Duke win; score: 106-72
    - Duke vs. Boston University: Reel 1, 1993 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3011)
    - Duke vs. Boston University: Reel 2, 1993 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3012)
    - Duke vs. Boston University: Reel 3, 1993 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3013)
    - Duke vs. Boston University: Reel 4, 1993 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3014)
  - Oklahoma, 1993 January 04
    Duke win; score: 88-84
    - Duke vs. Oklahoma: Reel 1, 1993 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3015)
    - Duke vs. Oklahoma: Reel 2, 1993 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3016)
    - Duke vs. Oklahoma: Reel 3, 1993 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3017)
    - Duke vs. Oklahoma: Reel 4, 1993 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3018)
  - Georgia Tech, 1993 January 09
    Duke loss; score: 79-80
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1993 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3019)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1993 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3020)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1993 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3021)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 4, 1993 January 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3022)
  - Wake Forest, 1993 January 13
    Duke loss; score: 86-98
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1993 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3023)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1993 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3024)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1993 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3025)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1993 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3026)
  - Iowa, 1993 January 16
    Duke win; score: 65-56
    - Duke vs. Iowa: Reel 1, 1993 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3027)
    - Duke vs. Iowa: Reel 2, 1993 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3028)
    - Duke vs. Iowa: Reel 3, 1993 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3029)
    - Duke vs. Iowa: Reel 4, 1993 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3030)
  - Virginia, 1993 January 17
    Duke loss; score: 69-77
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1993 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3031)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1993 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3032)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1993 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3033)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1993 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3034)
  - NC State, 1993 January 21
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1993 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3035)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1993 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3036)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1993 January 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3037)
  - Florida State, 1993 January 24
    Duke loss; score: 88-89
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 1, 1993 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3038)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 2, 1993 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3039)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 3, 1993 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3040)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 4, 1993 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 137, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3041)
  - San Francisco, 1993 January 26
    Duke win; score: 117-73
    - Duke vs. San Francisco: Reel 1, 1993 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 138, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3042)
    - Duke vs. San Francisco: Reel 2, 1993 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 138, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3043)
    - Duke vs. San Francisco: Reel 3, 1993 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 138, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3044)
    - Duke vs. San Francisco: Reel 4, 1993 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 138, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3045)
  - Maryland, 1993 January 30
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1993 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 138, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3046)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1993 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 138, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3047)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1993 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 138, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3048)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1993 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 138, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3049)
  - North Carolina, 1993 February 03
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1993 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 138, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3050)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1993 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 138, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3051)